<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>egoodwin.io</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>https://egoodwin.io/</link>
    
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2023, Calvin Tran</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 21:55:05 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Hugo - gohugo.io</generator>
    <docs>http://cyber.harvard.edu/rss/rss.html</docs>
    <atom:link href="https://egoodwin.io//atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Procrastination2</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/procrastination2/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t know what it says about me that whenever I&amp;rsquo;m feeling overwhelmed with things to do I get this urge to modify me emacs config files.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/procrastination2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 21:55:05 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Github Pages DNS</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/github_dns/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I just spent way longer than I should have configuring DNS to handle GitHub Pages verification process. I&amp;rsquo;ve enabled https now and verified the domain.  I had no idea that GitHub Pages squatting had become so problematic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, onwards and upwards.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/github_dns/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:04:16 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That felt good! Dynamo vs. Galaxy</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/dynamo_la/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What a game! Not the prettiest soccer I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen, but being in the stands for the Dynamo/LA Galaxy game felt good. At this point we&amp;rsquo;ve:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Been undefeated at home this season&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintained a clean sheet at home for all three games&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Got a player (Amine Bassi) who has gone four games and scored a penalty shot in each game. This is the longest consecutive penalty shot streak in MLS history.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Got a solid back-line and midfield setup that can manuever around the field and create open spaces to play into as well as service from the back.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a team that is controlling the ball and is generally possessive for most of the game.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What we don&amp;rsquo;t have:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Someone who can consistently get in the penalty box and effectively shoot on goal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What the LA Galaxy game showed us was a team that is effectively playing together, trusting each other to play their positions and getting creative on how to open up the opponents defense. Ben Olsen promised us that you would see more players crashing the box and that is what we saw.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And our defense! I LOVE our defensive line! Bartlow, Hadebe, Steres, Clark&amp;hellip;legitimately fun to watch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He also promised us a gritty play style that punished opponents and wore them down. If the number of fights on the field and red cards on Saturday was any indication, these players got under the LA Galaxy&amp;rsquo;s skin and made them lose their cool. When the fights broke out, the fans went ballistic as well, showing that Houston&amp;rsquo;s desire to bleed orange is there, ready to be rekindled with a team that can be dependable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A 3-0 victory felt nice! And if you think about the fact that 2 of the 3 teams we&amp;rsquo;ve lost to this season are sitting at the top of the league (and deserve to be there), our record is looking pretty positive at this point. We&amp;rsquo;re definitely a work in progress, but I&amp;rsquo;m feeling really good about the fact that this team is lightyears ahead of last year and the year before.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/dynamo_la/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 20:40:54 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Kinane&#39;s new special is amazing</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/kyle_kinane/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nothing more to say other than the title.  Kyle Kinane&amp;rsquo;s new special is amazing! It&amp;rsquo;s going to be released on YouTube on March 30th, but I was more than happy to pay for the paid release version on &lt;a href=&#34;https://800poundgorillamedia.com/pages/kyle-kinane-shocks-struts&#34;&gt;800 Pound Gorilla&lt;/a&gt;. Highly recommend you do the same!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://player.vimeo.com/video/804372880?h=9e8c3843de&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;360&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;autoplay; fullscreen; picture-in-picture&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://vimeo.com/804372880&#34;&gt;Kyle Kinane Trailer V1&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href=&#34;https://vimeo.com/user185717636&#34;&gt;Ian&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://vimeo.com&#34;&gt;Vimeo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/kyle_kinane/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 08:27:20 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynamo Home Opener vs. Austin FC</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/dynamo_opener/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last night was the first Houston Dynamo home game of the season. For a lot of reasons I was excited for this one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;new-ownership--management&#34;&gt;New Ownership &amp;amp; Management&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New owner Ted Segal bought into the club at the end of the 2021 season, and since then has proven that he&amp;rsquo;s serious about making this club a serious contender in the league, and is willing to invest to do so. This season opener was the first opportunity to get a glimpse of what that might look like. Sure, last season included the signing of Hector Herrera, a top Mexican player from Atletico Madrid, but this was the first full offseason that the new ownership has had to sign new players, upgrade the facilities, and make front and back-office staff changes. I won&amp;rsquo;t go into everything that&amp;rsquo;s been done, but I point all this out because one of the changes involved upgrades to Shell Energy stadium.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-new-stadium&#34;&gt;The New Stadium&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shell Energy Stadium (formerly PNC Stadium, formerly BBVA Stadium) got a pretty drastic facelift over the summer. New mesh seating was installed, new restaurant contracts were signed, and the East portion of the stadium was fitted with a new East Club experience geared towards more high-rolling fans and corporate seating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was eager to check out the changes firsthand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Upon walking in, the hallways to the stadium looked refreshed, but largely the same at first glance. As you went further in, you noticed the new restaurants that were operating. The smells of the food were much more pleasant and apparent, as there were a lot of unique flavors available for purchase (BBQ, Mexican, and Vietnamese via Roostar).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But heading out to the field was a whole different matter. The seats are NICE! Very comfortable, and the field looks like a modern club stadium fitting of a city like Houston.  Overall, the facelift modernizes the stadium, and I&amp;rsquo;m excited to be able to watch the rest of the season in this environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-game&#34;&gt;The Game&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s no secret by now that the Dynamo got the 3 points with a 2-0 game over Austin FC. Austin is a tough rival, but this was their third game in the last week, so one can be forgiven for not reading too much into this victory. Having said that, there were lots of positives about this game for a fan who was watched this team scrape bottom of the league for the better part of a decade.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The game was a blast. The Dynamo didn&amp;rsquo;t have many moments of brilliance, but they managed to get the ball in the back of the net. Steve Clark had a really solid game at goalkeeper and kept the clean sheet. Hector Herrera eschewed his usual position of defending midfielder and pressed forward to attack and scored his first goal since signing with the team. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if this was part of the original game plan, or just him being a team captain and showing the newer guys how it&amp;rsquo;s done. Regardless, his goal off of a great give-and-take assist from Griffin Dorsey showed that this team is figuring out how to link up inside the box and can be dangerous if you&amp;rsquo;re not paying attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s still a VERY new team, and they haven&amp;rsquo;t had a chance to solidify how they&amp;rsquo;re all going to play together. Because of this there were plenty of sloppy passes, incoherent play execution and general mistake-making. However, they all played aggressively and dominated most of the important stats (shots on goal, passes, corner kicks).  Also, I was shocked at how physical our players were in comparison to Austin, especially in the second half.  Amine Bassi is shorter than most of the Austin team, but he looked positively ecstatic to be bodying a number of their players throughout the game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not calling this team a finished product at this point, but I am optimistic about what next season will bring. I may even be convinced to be optimistic about this season if they get more polished, but maintain this level of intensity throughout the season.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/dynamo_opener/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 00:01:47 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why now?</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/why_now/</link>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;its-2023who-the-heck-is-still-blogging&#34;&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s 2023&amp;hellip;who the heck is still blogging?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve never been a committed blogger. I&amp;rsquo;ve created six or seven different blogs in my lifetime, including rolling my own static blog engine back in the day, and let them die out over time.  I was an early adopter of &lt;a href=&#34;https://radio.userland.com&#34;&gt;Userland Radio&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://blogger.com/&#34;&gt;Blogger&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://tumblr.com&#34;&gt;Tumblr&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, why this blog? Why now?  In short, the tools have just become so easy and so controllable, and the world has become more interesting, and I feel like I have something to say. I don&amp;rsquo;t really have an agenda with this blog, but I do have a point of view on a number of topics. Sitting at the intersection of Finance and Technology gives me a vantage point that I&amp;rsquo;ve learned is rather unique.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, my initial intent is to blog about topics that interest me. Soccer (particularly the Dynamo and MLS in the US), Wall Street, practical programming concepts, tech projects and finance/economics,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m old enough now to realize I&amp;rsquo;m mostly doing this for me. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to have you along for the ride, though.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/why_now/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 13:23:38 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/first-post/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;First post on Hugo!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 23:35:56 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
