<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on egoodwin.io</title>
    <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on egoodwin.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 21:59:31 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://egoodwin.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Linkroll - March 1, 2026</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/linkroll_2026_03_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 21:59:31 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/linkroll_2026_03_01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://crooked.com/podcast/the-enshittification-of-the-internet-with-cory-doctorow/&#34;&gt;Cory Doctorow on the Offline Podcast talking about enshittification&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.hp.com/hp-linux-imaging-and-printing&#34;&gt;HP Linux Imaging and Printing&lt;/a&gt; - currently wrestling getting my discontinued HP printer on Linux.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://9front.org/releases/2025/10/11/0/&#34;&gt;9Front released &amp;ldquo;Release&amp;rdquo; back in November&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing around with &lt;a href=&#34;https://grapheneos.org/&#34;&gt;Graphene OS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.openbsd.org/&#34;&gt;OpenBSD 7.8 has been released&lt;/a&gt; and it has Raspberry Pi support.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/eugeneyan/open-llms&#34;&gt;Open Source LLM models&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/LukeSmithxyz/emailwiz&#34;&gt;EmailWiz&lt;/a&gt; - script to set up a linux mailserver&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/@yayasaafan/mastering-dbcontext-in-entity-framework-core-configuration-lifetime-and-best-practices-e8e89037d34d&#34;&gt;Overview of DbContext in EntityFrameworkCore&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starting up again</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/starting_up_again/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:44:49 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/starting_up_again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After a two year hiatus, I&amp;rsquo;m back to chronicling my thoughts online. I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking alot about the early days of the internet and how much fun it was to be a part of it. Blogrolls and RSS feeds and just feeling like you could roll your own blog software and make something that was functional.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Maybe its all the AI talk about how content&amp;rsquo;s not going to matter anymore, because the bots are going to just autogenerate it for you now. I&amp;rsquo;ve always liked an underdog story, so maybe its time to revive human-generated content at the tail end of the human internet. At the very least it will be training material for the machines :)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gary Gulman&#39;s Born on 3rd Base</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/gary_gulman_born_on_3rd_base/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:42:26 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/gary_gulman_born_on_3rd_base/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The new Gary Gulman comedy special (streaming on Max) is amazing. Let&amp;rsquo;s face it, I&amp;rsquo;m probably never going to write about a comedy special that I don&amp;rsquo;t think is amazing, but Gary Gulman is a master of the craft and one of the all-time greats.  He&amp;rsquo;s a comedian&amp;rsquo;s comedian and I devour everything he creates. This special does not disappoint.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Called &amp;ldquo;Born on 3rd Base&amp;rdquo;, the special is a great follow-up to his last special &amp;ldquo;The Great Depresh&amp;rdquo;. The last special was an honest look into the darkness of coming to grips with his crippling depression and getting much needed treatment. It shed a light on mental illness in a sympathetic and warm way that both entertained and humanized the topic. This special at first glance leaves all that behind and deals with broader social topics of income inequality and social stigmas.  But dig just a little bit beneath the surface and you&amp;rsquo;ll see that &lt;em&gt;Born on 3rd Base&lt;/em&gt; subtly explores the environment and relationships in his life that fed his depression growing up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Link Roundup</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/link_roundup_20230908/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 14:55:41 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/link_roundup_20230908/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/tKydpb0z6i0?si=5Z71YYnu9uHqRfWr&#34;&gt;The incredible philosophy of Ange Postecoglou&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://swift.org/&#34;&gt;Swift.org&lt;/a&gt; The Swift homepage got a facelift with more tutorials&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/HhxryWYTR28?si=6G-9xOP-_zFJnfTJ&#34;&gt;Blocking a Floating Tremolo on a Guitar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bsdnow.tv/&#34;&gt;BSD Now podcast&lt;/a&gt; - I&amp;rsquo;m really enjoying this podcast&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://runbsd.info/&#34;&gt;RunBSD.info&lt;/a&gt; - who uses BSD and why?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/hgN8pCMLI2U?si=iq4ptDn0lwPcOvk4&#34;&gt;The History of BSD Jails&lt;/a&gt; - I&amp;rsquo;m always amazed at how little work BSD Jails are and how much work Docker is&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/I49pJqR-USY?si=gfxqd-x4KnXEfqAN&#34;&gt;LawrenceTV&lt;/a&gt; - more people need to love Lawrence as much as I do&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Being Clever</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/being_clever/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 12:37:23 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/being_clever/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing a lot of thinking about coding styles lately.  One of the interesting things about the space that my firm plays in is that it attracts people that are technologically inclined but have not typically had prior coding experience. A lot of the folks come from accounting and finance backgrounds. As such, they don&amp;rsquo;t have the background in things like version control, CI/CD, code reuse and refactoring, or any sort of true development best practices.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I play Xonotic now</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/xonotic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:28:39 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/xonotic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://freebsd.org/&#34;&gt;FreeBSD&lt;/a&gt; has been my server operating system of choice for the past two decades. I may have started on Linux (with a &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Walnut_Creek_CDROM&#34;&gt;Walnut Creek&lt;/a&gt; CD of Linux Slackware), but after I got out of university I started toying around with the *BSD flavors (particularly FreeBSD and OpenBSD). FreeBSD is clean, has sensible defaults, and frankly, the ports and package system is just hassle-free when it comes to getting up and running. If you&amp;rsquo;re at all wanting a Unix system that is dependable, a great platform for development, and running simple services, FreeBSD is hard to beat.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ups and Downs of Being a Dynamo Fan</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/ups_and_downs_of_being_a_dynamo_fan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 11:29:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/ups_and_downs_of_being_a_dynamo_fan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Being a Dynamo fan is not for the faint of heart. After a decade of malinvestment and terrible strategy moves (e.g. permanently trading away an international player slot on the roster), a definite case could be made that it&amp;rsquo;s easier building an expansion team franchise from scratch than rebuilding the Dynamo. And after seeing St. Louis and FC Cincinnati this year, I don&amp;rsquo;t think many would argue the reverse.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Still, a lot has been accomplished in a relatively short amount of time, and hope springs eternal in H-Town.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Procrastination</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/procrastination2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 21:55:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/procrastination2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t know what it says about me that, whenever I&amp;rsquo;m feeling overwhelmed with things to do, I get this urge to modify me emacs config files.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Github Pages DNS</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/github_dns/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:04:16 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/github_dns/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I just spent way longer than I should have configuring DNS to handle GitHub Pages verification process. I&amp;rsquo;ve enabled https now and verified the domain.  I had no idea that GitHub Pages squatting had become so problematic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Anyway, onwards and upwards.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That felt good! Dynamo vs. Galaxy</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/dynamo_la/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 20:40:54 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/dynamo_la/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What a game! Not the prettiest soccer I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen, but being in the stands for the Dynamo/LA Galaxy game felt good. At this point we&amp;rsquo;ve:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Been undefeated at home this season&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Maintained a clean sheet at home for all three games&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Got a player (Amine Bassi) who has gone four games and scored a penalty shot in each game. This is the longest consecutive penalty shot streak in MLS history.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Got a solid back-line and midfield setup that can manuever around the field and create open spaces to play into as well as service from the back.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Have a team that is controlling the ball and is generally possessive for most of the game.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What we don&amp;rsquo;t have:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Kinane&#39;s new special is amazing</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/kyle_kinane/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 08:27:20 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/kyle_kinane/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nothing more to say other than the title.  Kyle Kinane&amp;rsquo;s new special is amazing! It&amp;rsquo;s going to be released on YouTube on March 30th, but I was more than happy to pay for the paid release version on &lt;a href=&#34;https://800poundgorillamedia.com/pages/kyle-kinane-shocks-struts&#34;&gt;800 Pound Gorilla&lt;/a&gt;. Highly recommend you do the same!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://player.vimeo.com/video/804372880?h=9e8c3843de&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;360&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;autoplay; fullscreen; picture-in-picture&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://vimeo.com/804372880&#34;&gt;Kyle Kinane Trailer V1&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href=&#34;https://vimeo.com/user185717636&#34;&gt;Ian&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://vimeo.com&#34;&gt;Vimeo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamo Home Opener vs. Austin FC</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/dynamo_opener/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 00:01:47 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/dynamo_opener/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last night was the first Houston Dynamo home game of the season. For a lot of reasons I was excited for this one.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;new-ownership--management&#34;&gt;New Ownership &amp;amp; Management&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New owner Ted Segal bought into the club at the end of the 2021 season, and since then has proven that he&amp;rsquo;s serious about making this club a serious contender in the league, and is willing to invest to do so. This season opener was the first opportunity to get a glimpse of what that might look like. Sure, last season included the signing of Hector Herrera, a top Mexican player from Atletico Madrid, but this was the first full offseason that the new ownership has had to sign new players, upgrade the facilities, and make front and back-office staff changes. I won&amp;rsquo;t go into everything that&amp;rsquo;s been done, but I point all this out because one of the changes involved upgrades to Shell Energy stadium.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why now?</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/why_now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 13:23:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/why_now/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;its-2023who-the-heck-is-still-blogging&#34;&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s 2023&amp;hellip;who the heck is still blogging?&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve never been a committed blogger. I&amp;rsquo;ve created six or seven different blogs in my lifetime, including rolling my own static blog engine back in the day, and let them die out over time.  I was an early adopter of &lt;a href=&#34;https://radio.userland.com&#34;&gt;Userland Radio&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://blogger.com/&#34;&gt;Blogger&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://tumblr.com&#34;&gt;Tumblr&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, why this blog? Why now?  In short, the tools have just become so easy and so controllable, and the world has become more interesting, and I feel like I have something to say. I don&amp;rsquo;t really have an agenda with this blog, but I do have a point of view on a number of topics. Sitting at the intersection of Finance and Technology gives me a vantage point that I&amp;rsquo;ve learned is rather unique.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 23:35:56 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;First post on Hugo!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
