<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on egoodwin.io</title>
    <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on egoodwin.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 21:55:05 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://egoodwin.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Procrastination2</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/procrastination2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 21:55:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/procrastination2/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t know what it says about me that whenever I&amp;rsquo;m overwhelmed I get this urge to modify me emacs config files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Github Pages DNS</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/github_dns/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:04:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/github_dns/</guid>
      <description>I just spent way longer than I should have configuring DNS to handle GitHub Pages verification process. I&amp;rsquo;ve enabled https now and verified the domain. I had no idea that GitHub Pages squatting had become so problematic.
Anyway, onwards and upwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That felt good! Dynamo vs. Galaxy</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/dynamo_la/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 20:40:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/dynamo_la/</guid>
      <description>What a game! Not the prettiest soccer I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen, but being in the stands for the Dynamo/LA Galaxy game felt good. At this point we&amp;rsquo;ve:
Been undefeated at home this season Maintained a clean sheet at home for all three games Got a player (Amine Bassi) who has gone four games and scored a penalty shot in each game. This is the longest consecutive penalty shot streak in MLS history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Kinane&#39;s new special is amazing</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/kyle_kinane/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 08:27:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/kyle_kinane/</guid>
      <description>Nothing more to say other than the title. Kyle Kinane&amp;rsquo;s new special is amazing! It&amp;rsquo;s going to be released on YouTube on March 30th, but I was more than happy to pay for the paid release version on 800 Pound Gorilla. Highly recommend you do the same!
Kyle Kinane Trailer V1 from Ian on Vimeo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynamo Home Opener vs. Austin FC</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/dynamo_opener/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 00:01:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/dynamo_opener/</guid>
      <description>Last night was the first Houston Dynamo home game of the season. For a lot of reasons I was excited for this one.
New Ownership &amp;amp; Management New owner Ted Segal bought into the club at the end of the 2021 season, and since then has proven that he&amp;rsquo;s serious about making this club a serious contender in the league, and is willing to invest to do so. This season opener was the first opportunity to get a glimpse of what that might look like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why now?</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/why_now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 13:23:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/why_now/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s 2023&amp;hellip;who the heck is still blogging? I&amp;rsquo;ve never been a committed blogger. I&amp;rsquo;ve created six or seven different blogs in my lifetime, including rolling my own static blog engine back in the day, and let them die out over time. I was an early adopter of Userland Radio, Blogger, and Tumblr.
So, why this blog? Why now? In short, the tools have just become so easy and so controllable, and the world has become more interesting, and I feel like I have something to say.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://egoodwin.io/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 23:35:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://egoodwin.io/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>First post on Hugo!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
